SPOOKY IN LOVE
CEO CHEON YEO-RI
EPISODE 2
PARK SEUNG-JAE, SOLE LEAD IN 3RD ROUND
…A SMOOTH COMEBACK
2) AUTOPSY REPORT
CUSTOM WIGS
BODY OF MS. JANG, PRO GOLFER
PARK SEUNG-JAE'S EX-GIRLFRIEND, FOUND
PARK SEUNG-JAE WANTED BY POLICE
AS PRIME SUSPECT
SHOCKING DISCOVERY ON HOTEL ROOFTOP,
PARK SEUNG-JAE UNDER INVESTIGATION
POLICE EXPAND INVESTIGATION,
PARK SEUNG-JAE ON SUSPECT LIST
SEARCH AND SEIZURE WARRANT
NAME OF SUSPECT: PARK SEUNG-JAE
CORRECTIONAL SERVICES ADVANCING THE FUTURE
BY BALANCING ORDER AND HUMAN RIGHTS
LIVE: PARK SEUNG-JAE'S FATHER,
ASSEMBLYMAN PARK JIN-DONG
EMERGENCY PRESS CONFERENCE
PARK DO-JUN? YOO HYE-WON
PROSECUTOR MA GANG-UK
RAYMOND
CEO KANG MIN-HWAN
SPOOKY IN LOVE